http://www.windrock.com/privacy/

Request for Quote
First Name*Last Name*Company*
Send me updates about Windrock products and add me to the email list.
Email*
Phone*CityState*AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingInternationalIf International Select "International" at the bottomZipCountry*Project DetailsProducts of Interest
Spotlight
6400 Portable Analyzer
Platinum
Windrock Enterprise
Windrock MD
Autobalance
Other
CAPTCHANameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Privacy
Windrock Inc. > Privacy
Privacy
Apergy respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy puts you in control of how your personal information is used in connection with our web site, www.apergy.com and www.windrock.com (“Apergy Web Site”). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and share personal and non-personal information we obtain from users of the Apergy Web Site. This Privacy Policy only applies to the Apergy Web Site. By using the Apergy Web Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy is complemented by our Terms of Use available at http://www.apergy.com.
This is the website of
Apergy Corporation
2445 Technology Forest Rd, Ste 900
The Woodlands, TX 77381
We can be reached via e-mail at info@apergy.com or you can call us at (281) 403-5772.
WHAT WE COLLECT
We may collect the following information:
(i) “Personal Information” – that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, and date of birth/age;
“Non-Personal Information” – that is, information about you or your activities through which you cannot be personally identified; and/or
Information related to customer surveys, promotions, and/or offers which may be Personal Information and/or Non-Personal Information (e.g., preferences, demographics, interests, etc.).
In situations where it is possible to do so, Non-Personal Information (as well as publicly available information) may be linked to Personal Information.
We may collect Personal and Non-Personal Information from users of the Apergy Web Site. We may also obtain such information from third parties.
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER
We require the information that we gather for various reasons including the following: (i) to understand your needs, provide you with a better service, and respond to your inquiries; (ii) for internal record keeping; (iii) for internal analysis; and (iv) to administer promotions, services (e.g., registration for webcasts, etc.) and offers for which you provided Personal Information and/or Non-Personal Information. Subject to the provisions below, we may also use this information for other marketing-related purposes.
We may use the information to improve our products and services, and to measure the number of visitors to the Apergy Web Site and the areas of the Web Site that are of most interest to visitors.
We may use the information to customize the web site.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax, mail, or other means unless you direct us not to do so.
We may use your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for our own marketing purposes, including, but not limited to notifying you of new services, offers or other information via mail, email, telephone, text message, and other means. If you do not want us to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such uses by notifying us in accordance with the procedure set forth below under the heading, “Controlling your Personal Information.”
We may share your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with our affiliates (i.e., affiliated businesses and operating companies) (collectively, “Apergy Affiliates”) for any purpose. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with Apergy Affiliates for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such uses by notifying us in accordance with the procedure set forth below under the heading, “Controlling your Personal Information.” Although you may request to opt-out of sharing your Personal Information for marketing purposes, we may share Personal Information with Apergy Affiliates for non-marketing purposes.
We may share your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with our business (and other) partners for joint marketing efforts, or for our business (and other) partners’ own marketing purposes. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with such third parties for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such uses by notifying us in accordance with the procedure set forth below under the heading, “Controlling your Personal Information.”
We may share your Personal Information with Apergy Affiliates or with unrelated third parties (including contractors who provide services to us) to assist with any of the uses of Personal and Non-Personal Information described herein. For example, we may share and/or provide your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with/to third parties that assist with the operation, administration, or maintenance of our site. The privacy policies of such third parties may also apply. We may also disclose your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information to third parties if disclosure is required to comply with applicable laws or regulations; or if disclosure is necessary to enforce our Privacy Policy and/or Terms of Use, to protect your safety or security, or the safety and security of our site or third parties.
SECURITY AND CONFIDENTIALITY
We are committed to ensuring that your Personal Information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, we undertake no obligation to maintain the confidentiality of non-confidential data such as feedback, questions, comments or ideas that you voluntarily provide to us (e.g., via the “Contact” tab or similar features on the Apergy Web Site). We reserve the right to use and disclose such non-confidential information as we deem appropriate. By voluntarily submitting feedback to us, you consent to these terms.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other web sites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other web site. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the web site in question.
CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your Personal Information in the following ways:
If you have previously not objected to us using your Personal Information for our direct marketing purposes, you may opt-out of receiving future marketing emails from us at any time by emailing us at info@apergy.com with your opt-out request.
If you want to opt-out of any new uses of information permitted by this Privacy Policy caused by changes in our information practices, you may do so by emailing us at info@apergy.com with your opt-out request.
If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with Apergy Affiliates and/or our business (and other) partners for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by emailing us at info@apergy.com with your opt-out request.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. Or, you may contact us if you wish to review or change your Personal Information by using the “Contact“ tab on our home page.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes at which time, you will have the ability to opt-out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically.
If you do not want to be contacted by us in the future (unless you initiate the contact), please let us know by sending us an email to info@apergy.com, writing us to the above address (located at the beginning of this Privacy Policy) or calling us at (281) 403-5772.
EU AND SWISS SAFE HARBOR FOR INTERNAL EMPLOYEE DATA
Apergy recognizes that the European Union (“EU”) has an “omnibus” data protection regime established pursuant to the European Data Protection Directive (95/46/EC) (the “Directive”) and that Switzerland has a comprehensive data protection law (together, “Data Privacy Laws”). Among other things, the Data Privacy Laws generally require “adequate protection” for the transfer of personally identifiable information about Apergy employees in the EU and Switzerland to Apergy operations in the United States. Apergy accordingly adheres to the requirements of the US/EU and US/Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Principles published by the US Department of Commerce (“Safe Harbor”) with respect to certain employee data received in the United States from our affiliated companies in the EU and Switzerland. For more information about Safe Harbor please refer to the US Department of Commerce website at www.export.gov/safeharbor/. Any individual in the EU or Switzerland who cannot resolve his or her issue directly with Apergy can contact the local data protection authority for further information and assistance. Apergy provides its EU and Swiss employees with more detailed information about its data handling practices through internal company policies.
PERSONS UNDER 18
We do not knowingly collect or allow the collection of Personal Information from persons under the age of 18. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under the age of 18 and believe that the person has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us at info@apergy.com.
BUSINESS TRANSACTIONS
We may share or transfer your Personal and Non-Personal Information if Apergy enters into, or is involved in, a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of some or all of its assets.
COOKIES
When you visit the Apergy Web Site, we may use “cookies” and similar technologies to help us recognize and serve you better. Cookies are small files that contain information sent by a web site that is saved on your computer’s hard drive. You may delete cookies from your computer or aset your browser to reject cookies. However, doing so may limit some functionalities of our site.
WEBSITE VISITORS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES
We make no representation that the practices described in this Privacy Policy are compliant with laws outside of the United States including those that apply to the collection, security, use, and disclosure of Personal Information.
* * *
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above email address, mailing address, or phone number.
